(Leonard:)Be mad at science.
(Sheldon:)Don't you dare use
science against me.
Science is my best friend!
(Sheldon:)Oh, good,
I'm back up to eight.
(Leonard:)Will you tell him
he's out of his mind.
(Penny:)Actually, I get what he's saying.
Yes! Nine!
(Sheldon:)Welcome back, buddy.
(Penny:)It's like if you're dating
someone you're not that into,
(Penny:)and then they break up with you
(Penny:)and then you want them
more than ever.
(Sheldon:)I have no idea what
she's talking about.
(Sheldon:)But we're ganging up on you
so I agree.
(Leonard:)Okay, Sheldon, what do you
want me to do,
(Leonard:)hide the information?
(Leonard:)If I don't publish it,
it's just a matter of time
(Leonard:)before someone else does.
(Sheldon:)No, no, of course
you have to publish.
(Sheldon:)That's your responsibility
as a scientist.
(Sheldon:)Doing otherwise
would be unethical.
(Sheldon:)You have no choice.
(Leonard:)Fine, I'll publish.
(Sheldon:)Can you believe this guy?
Oh, Raj did the dishes.
(Howard:)How do you know
I didn't do them?
(Bernadette:)Because once,
when all the knives were dirty,
(Bernadette:)you cut a bagel with your keys.